<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Game Stores</string>
    <string name="titleText">Gaming stores</string>
    <string name="storeDescriptionButton">ABOUT</string>
    <string name="searchGame">GAMES</string>
    <string name="searchButton">SEARCH</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="steamText">Steam is a video game digital distribution service and storefront by Valve. It was launched as a software client in September 2003 as a
        way for Valve to provide automatic updates for their games and expanded to distributing and offering third-party game publishers titles in late 2005.
        Steam offers various features like digital rights management DRM game server matchmaking and anti-cheat measures and social networking and game streaming
        services. It provides the user with automatic game updating saved game cloud synchronization and community features such as friends messaging in-game chat
        and a community market.</string>
    <string name="steamTitle">STEAM</string>
    <string name="epicText">Epic Games, Inc. is an American video game and software developer and publisher based in Cary, North Carolina. The company was founded
        by Tim Sweeney as Potomac Computer Systems in 1991, originally located in his parents house in Potomac, Maryland.Epic Games develops Unreal Engine,
        a commercially available game engine which also powers their internally developed video games,
        such as Fortnite and the Unreal, Gears of War and Infinity Blade series.</string>
    <string name="epicTitle">EPIC</string>
    <string name="originText">The Origin store allows users to browse and purchase games from Electronic Arts catalogs. Instead of receiving a box, disc, or even CD key,
        purchased software is immediately attached to the users Origin account and is to be downloaded with the corresponding Origin client.
        Origin guarantees download availability forever after purchase, and there is no limit to the number of times a game can be downloaded.</string>
    <string name="originTitle">ORIGIN</string>
</resources>